So now Ribbon, our topic today is about
HDFC Ergo's Pratima Restore
Health Insurance Plan
versus Tiger Zip President Insurance
Plan. You should definitely
subscribe to both of these. Both are general
insurance companies and very trustworthy
companies. Talking about these ranges, in one company,
this 5 lakh subscription is for hospitalization
subscription. The sub-inspector
is Discover and post hospitalization insurance will
cover this treatment. You can also subscribe to
organ donor insurance, organ donor Dhairya Restore
benefit, stitch service service and any
family member can be given eight-point appointment and next to this,
you can subscribe
to restore once, which is equal to
the Avengers, whereas in Tata AIG,
this is the yoga of loot, Dhairya and Agni, which
means that no policy holder can
visit the hospital. Hospitalization is
not available in the hospital. So, in this mission,
both the companies have Ayurvedic
treatment service, whereas Yuvraj Emergency
Ambulance, if you can subscribe,
subscribe to
504A specialization, panel hospital.
Talking about the abs, both the
accused will be appointed as ambulance
Dhund provides ambulance facility.
If you subscribe to
Quip Habits policy and you run it regularly for 2 years, you can get
dental treatment up to 110 thousand rupees,
which can be appointed on your route.
Dental treatment
facility is available in shares for a noble cover which should be
diagnosed in war but young India.
After that, you
can subscribe to the treatment.
Option in shares is available in this benefit. If you
take Voltage's medical care premium policy for four years, then after that you can appoint 60 thousand rupees
for baby girl and 50,000 rupees for the daughter.
Well, there is no doubt that
you will get four years of subscription for Dhobi. It is
necessary to have a play appointment. You can also click on this in a live-in relationship.
If a girl is
subscribed, then her
VAT Fragrant Habit will be a three-year old
account, which is a very good thing. A
family floater policy of 25 lakhs to the school.
120 offers
₹5,000 per year on a 10 lakh policy in two years.
You can also subscribe to the designated service center for your treatment. You can also
subscribe to the
designated OPD service center for treatment.
Tata's policy also offers
OPD treatment. If you continue with the Tata
AIG policy for two years, you can get up
to two subscriptions. The
PIN verification is mandatory on these same MILK Tides. The same service center is available. In Tata AIG,
if you want more than
this, you
can take coverage in this. Many senior
leaders have to take Mirwaiz, whereas
in Tata AIG, it is inbuilt.
Consumables mean that whoever
listens to your pain more than the CPI(M) does not do all this on their own.
However, you have an inbuilt accidental death
benefit. If you cancel the policy and the
policyholder dies, whatever
your expenses may be.  And it is given to your nominee,
this option is not available in D, it is
available in subscribe, you have to keep in mind
that this midriff dental college is not available,
complete travels, if any policy
holder falls ill in some other city,
his family has to travel and go there, if
this has to be done then you
can click on Ghr Shyam, option is available in share,
service service was done for 2 years and the channel
gives subscription when school time subscribes
and three year policy subscribes
when appointment is made in the middle of the product to
select the insurance plan, like it,
if you liked the video then actually we
call it information, so please like our channel and
subscribe, thank you for